

# **Arun Kumar Maurya**

• 791112, Doimukh, India

+91 8837352664

Location Preferred : Papum Pare, Capital Complex Itanagar □ aroonmauryan1@gmail.com

1995 Sep 12

### **Profile**

A well-organized educator with experience in teaching, mentoring. Have a proven track record of successfully teaching. Ability to work together with others and manage issues and disputes in a professional manner. Have the ability to convey complicated details in a straightforward and enjoyable manner. I'd like to contribute my experience and expertise to a school that provides real career development opportunities.

## Education

Bachelor of Education,

VIVEKANAND KENDRA VIDYALAYA 2018 – 2020 7.26 CGPA

North Eastern Regional Institute of Science and Technology, MSc (Honours in Mathematics)

2015 – 2018 7.11 CGPA

B.SC (Honours in Mathematics),

Dera Natung Government College 2012 – 2015 51.4%

#### **Additional Information**

**Permanent** Address - S/o Vijoy Shankar Maurya Vill:- Uttarai, Maryadpur, Mau,

Uttar Pradesh - 221602

Communication Address - S/o Vijoy Shankar Maurya

Vill:- Midpu II, Doimukh, Papum Pare,

Arunachal Pradesh - 791112

# **Professional Experience**

**Teacher**, *Arun valley public school* 2020 – 2021

Created lesson plains for various classes meeting with parents and school board members; maintaining classroom discipline; methodically providing support for lesson; simplifying lessons plans in line with curriculum objectives; and assisting in preparing for school exams.

Senior Teacher, New Galaxy Academy

2017 - 2018

Responsible for ensuring that all students fully comprehended the taught curriculum and for providing assistance to students who needed it. Adopted unique teaching methods, recorded all lessons, facilitated healthy group conversations, and provided guidance to struggling students.

**Diploma in Computer Application** 

Duration: 1 year

#### **Skills**

Effective classroom management

*Time management*, *Conflict resolution* 

Verbal & Written communication

Technological savvy

Excel, Word

# Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Bhojpuri
- Assamese

## **Declaration**

I, Arun Kumar Maurya do hereby declare that all statements mentioned above are true to the best of my knowledge and belief. I will be able to provide the necessary documents wphenever required.

